A sound soul dwells within a sound mind and a sound body.
What can we fund now and sound to you about?
In this book we have nothing to do with comes in mind compared to jumping on a ladder that isii.
In this book Kenobi, we are waiting for this agenda to arrive.
You may notice where there is a LM deck there.
Fools!
言葉よりもっと強い響きが 今聞こえるか
六人目も合わさず 運命まで絡んでく
行き先もらったポテル 食えない夜の端で
不可愛しすぎた眩しさが 悪い夢に続いても
繋いだ魂の火が胸を刺すなら
言葉よりもっと強い響きが 今聞こえるか
やっと理由は途絶びに 突きつけられて
触れた瞬間の傷の分だけ 確かになれる
ご視聴ありがとうございました
The wind of this holy sword extends back through all of living memory.
It waits, sleeping silently throughout the years.
He who draws the holy sword from the ground will be deemed a hero
and shall receive everlasting glory and fame as a mighty king.
He shall rise above all others. Adorned with wings of light, he shall stride through the skies.
With a single swing, he shall cut through space itself.
The holy sword is a true warrior, cutting down all those who stand in opposition.
But forget not that all of his greatness and triumph shall be brought about by the holy sword.
Forever shall the stories of the holy sword's mighty deeds be passed down.
For all eternity shall the name of the holy sword be remembered, exalted, and honored.
The holy sword, Excalibur.
And now appears a brave youth boldly seeking to create his own place in this legendary tale of glory and greatness.
His name...
Holy Sword!
Legend of the Holy Sword 2.
Wanna go drinking, gambling, and playing?
This is the holy sword.
This is the holy sword, which is the holy sword.
How very...
lame.
Hmm?
Young lad.
How are you called?
Me?
Uh, well, my name is Ock's poor.
Fool!
Oh, no, I'm not a fool.
You see, I'm at the top of my class at the DWMA.
I really am quite intelligent.
Fool!
Oh, I'm telling you, I'm not a fool.
My legend dates back to the 12th century, you see.
My legend is quite old.
The 12th century was a long time ago.
Do you want to hear my heroic tale?
Uh, yes, of course I do.
That's why I came here in the first...
Now then, if you are to be my associate,
there are 1,000 provisions you must observe.
You will need to peruse these before we begin our partnership.
I'm sorry, but could you tell me in what way I'm being a fool?
Fool!
You have no need for that information.
Oh, if you say so.
My morning always begins with a cup of coffee with cream.
Do you know why?
Uh, no, I do...
Fool!
Listen, boy.
My morning begins with a cup of coffee with cream.
Plus, every morning I begin my day with a cup of coffee with cream.
But you just said nothing beats a cup of...
This is the first of 1,000 provisions.
My mornings always begin with a cup of coffee with cream.
Don't forget it.
But, as I just pointed out, you said nothing beats a cup of tea.
Here, I want to show you something.
So, these people...
Are they your family?
The woman's tending next to you.
Don't tell me she's your...
Of course they're my family.
Isn't it obvious?
And a wonderful family they were.
Past tense.
It happened long ago, when I was still in the flower of my youth.
The cities began to grow wild.
People lost hope for the future.
They became lazy, idle time wasters.
And to my everlasting shame, I was no exception.
Someday, I'll have enough money saved to leave this city for good.
Thus, I began to watch the 7 o'clock news religiously every night.
I see.
So, that pretty girl I saw in the picture was just...
That has nothing to do with it.
Uh, then what does it have to do with...
Honestly, you don't get it at all.
What am I not getting?
Number 58 of the 1,000 provisions I would like you to observe.
Never talk to me while I'm humming to myself.
This is an important provision.
Do you understand?
Uh, I can't help but notice that your stories and these provisions
don't really seem to be connected in any significant way.
Humming in the nightly news share a very tight connection indeed.
But from what you just told me about your past, I thought...
A symphony cannot be created using common sense and probabilities.
It is already written in the fate of the composer.
No, that's not it.
A symphony is the inevitable result of a bad childhood,
deafness, and too many beans eaten after a certain time of day.
Obviously.
Thus, I found myself carrying the fate of the entire troupe
as I performed my dance before a capacity crowd at the Opera House.
Wait, what?
Thank you.
Here we go.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
I am stuffed
This is nice, I'm glad we decided to do it
Getting everyone together for no other reason than to hang out and enjoy each other's company
It's peaceful, don't you think?
That may have to change, I can't stand out if it's peaceful
I'll just have to shake things up a little, bring on a big old black star
Hey, Tsubaki
Yes, what is it?
Have you finished writing that report we were assigned in class last week yet?
You mean you still haven't finished it?
You should hurry, isn't it due tomorrow?
Yeah, I know, but it is that kind of report, so
Oh, it's that kind, huh?
Do you think you could help me, Tsubaki, pretty please?
I don't get it, I wasn't even saying anything then
Uh, excuse me
Mr. Excalibur, sir?
Mr. Excalibur, hello?
Hello?
You still alive in there?
Fool!
One must take time to think
Rushing forward without considering things beforehand is the height of foolishness
Ah, yes
That reminds me of another time when I had to consider things
That case was long ago, but I remember it still
It was back when I still hung my hat on Baker Street and called it home
Holmes, have you deduced anything yet?
Of course I have, Watson
It appears the perpetrator's depravity is equal to his stupidity based upon the elementary trick he has seen fit to employ here
Elementary?
But we're stumped
The door was locked from the inside
Fool!
Huh?
Precisely, Excalibur, couldn't have said it better myself
Watson, you're indeed a fool
But Holmes, now Excalibur, will you explain to us what you see here?
Use your impeccable logic and great intelligence to solve the puzzle of the locked room and point out the killer so we can apprehend him
It's quite basic, actually
Perhaps the simplest of tricks there is
True, it may not seem so simple from an ordinary person's point of view
Some people may even consider it a baffling, utterly perplexing problem
Things will often appear complicated on the outside, while in truth they are simplicity itself
Of course, how one sees these things depends on the person
Many people find that there is a fine line separating the very complex from the very simple
Okay, Excalibur, I think we get your point
Could you please just solve the case now?
Fool!
You understand nothing
Yes, well, you're spot on there
Okay, I'm a fool, now please explain the perpetrator's trick
The trick is so elementary that there's no need for an explanation
The killer is
You
What, me?
And thus, the case was brilliantly solved
Are you sure Watson was really the killer? That seems somewhat unlike
To sum up, this brings us to number 278 of the 1,000 provisions you must observe
I hate carrots
Never even think about putting them in my food, get it?
Yeah, I hate carrots too
Silence!
This is number 349 of the 1,000 provisions you must observe
Meisters should eat everything, regardless of personal likes and dislikes
Never say anything as selfish as, I don't like carrots, again
But that contradictor
Do you know what kind of terrible tragedy such indiscretion can lead to?
Perhaps this anecdote will help you understand it better
These events occurred just after my legend began in the 12th century
When I accompanied the Meister King Arthur on an expedition to Rome
Facing an army of this magnitude will be arduous, Excalibur
Saying such a thing isn't like you, Arthur
You mustn't lose heart
Excalibur
The Knights of the Round Table never give up
No matter what
You must remember that
You swore an oath
Of course, you're right
I forgot myself
My comrades are depending on me
We fight on for their sake
Yes, we fight for them, Excalibur
Will you lend me your strength now?
Of course
And thus, my journey with King Arthur continued on
Your personality seemed a lot different in that
To sum up, that is what led to number 679 of the 1,000 provisions you must observe
Always place a dehumidifier in your room
So, how long have you been the kind of guy you are today?
From what I have told you thus far, you can no doubt ascertain that I was once a lowly, rough-and-tumble sort of person
Never mind, forget I asked
Listen up, everyone
Drinks are on me today
Drink all you want
Hey, Excalibur
You're an incredible man, you know that?
I was all dried up
Yes, nothing could satisfy me anymore
I was but a shell of a man
An unspeakable emptiness grew deep inside my heart
I became frustrated, sad, hollow
The gaping hole inside of me was growing larger every day
Slowly consuming me from the inside out
At least until that day came
Excalibur, I'm so happy
Excalibur, hurry, come here
I want to tell you something, Excalibur
I love you with all my heart
If only every day could be like this
You don't need to worry about that
I'm not going anywhere
I'm afraid you don't understand
The day will come when your kindness is too great for me
Your love will begin to weigh me down
And I will need my freedom
I don't understand
What are you talking about, Kathy?
Oh, Excalibur
Please remember this, if nothing else
I'll always love you no matter what happens
You have to remember that
Promise me that you will remember
I promise you, I will remember
However, just as she had predicted
Our time together did not last long
There was to be no happily ever after for us
Thus
What? It ends there?
Thus at long last the fighting between the rival gangs ended
But what happened?
To sum up, this leads us to number 778 of the 1,000 provisions you must observe
Never mail a letter without the return address and the proper postage
And don't call collect
I wonder what happened with the pretty girl
Hmm?
What looks like you just said, Yagwan?
I... I said I wonder what happened with the pretty girl
Hmm
You wish to know what happened next?
As a gesture of respect for your inquiry and interest
I will sing you a song
How does me wanting to know what happened make you want to sing?
Fool!
As someone who is unaware of the vital role that singing has played in the cultural history of mankind
You are in no position to question me
Remember that the next time you stop to consider your place in this world
You do not possess the power to deny a singer his song
Do you understand what I'm telling you?
Uh... yeah
And I shall begin
Here we go
Excalibur
From the United Kingdom
I'm looking for heaven
I'm going to California
Excalibur
How long is this torture going to last?
Well, I think that about covers the 1,000 provisions that you are required to observe
Oh, the humanity
Now I would like for you to participate in the most important provision
Number 452
The 5-Hour Storytelling Party
You are chosen
It shall all be yours
Victory
And glory
You shall rule the world
Reigning above all others as a mighty warrior king
So let us go home together
For victory
And for glory
Excuse me, young lad
What is the meaning of this?
Oh, I'm sorry
But I already have a partner
So I really should be going here
Uh-huh
Then why did you come here?
Well, funny story
I had originally intended to write about you
For a report I was assigned in school
But you're lame, so forget it
Oh, I never finish my report
I'm going to be in big trouble
Hey, Blackstar
Did you finish the report that was due today?
Yeah
I got it right here
It's only one page
Don't you think that's a little short?
Of course it's short
Why wouldn't it be?
There's only one word for that thing
So what word did you write?
Go!
Thank you.
You are a warrior, don't you? So why not test yourself by mastering me? Only one person can have this honor, so act quickly.
Observe my exquisite form. Notice my unparalleled sharpness. Act now and you'll receive four free hours at my five-hour storytelling party.
Enter yourself in my special drawing. I will be teaming up with the winning Meister. Don't let this chance pass you by. Send entries to the address below. May victory and glory be yours.
Lame!
Boy, am I glad I didn't get involved with that Excalibur mess.
You're lame.
Hey, Ox, I've been meaning to ask you something.
Oh, is it about my stylish hairdo?
No, it's not that.
Then my custom-made glasses, perhaps.
Not that either.
What then?
Tell me, do you wear boxers or briefs?
You're lame.
On the next episode of Soul Eater, the Eve party nightmare. And so the curtain rises?
By the way, I wear briefs.
I stand on my couch.
It's not that big.
Then let's just versus in the Speci Academy.
How does it take place?
Good luck in the Westernской Division.
I hope it's a positive luck in the dry season.